let quiz = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of the first covid vaccine approved for emergency use in India?",
        option: [
            "Covaxin",
            "Covishield",
            "Bilogical E",
            "Sputnik V",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "The International Literacy Day is observed on?",
        option: [
            "SEP 22",
            "NOV 28",
            "SEP 8",
            "NOV 2"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these sounds would you associate with the heart?",
        option: [
            "CHIT CHIT",
            "PIT PIT",
            "DHAK DHAK"
            "CLICK CLICK",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "The language of Lakshadweep. a Union Territory of India, is",
        option: [
            "MALYALAM",
            "PUNJABI",
            "HINDI",
            "TAMIL",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "In which group of places the Kumbha Mela is held every twelve years?"
        option: [
            "Ujjain. Purl; Prayag. Haridwar",
            "Rameshwaram. Purl, Badrinath. Dwarika",
            "Chittakoot, Ujjain, Prayag,'Haridwar",
            "Prayag. Haridwar, Ujjain,. Nasik",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the correct HTML tag for the largest heading",
        option: ["<heading>", "<h6>", "<head>", "<h1>"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What are the terms 3G, 4G and 5G related to?",
        option: [
            "PHONE NETWORKS",
            "POPULATION GENERATION",
            "DIGITAL CAMERA",
            "GRADING IN SCHOOL",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "In 2008, Rajasthan Royals became the first winner of which annual sporting event?",
        option: ["PKL", "ISL", "PHL", "IPL"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Bahubali festival is related to"
        option: ["ISLAM", "HINDU", "BUDDHISM", "JAINISM"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the current president of U.S.A",
        option: ["Donald Trump", "Kamla harrish", "Joe Biden", "Barrack Obama"],
        answer: 3,
    },
];
